The sky is shining
It's a picnic, but I can't forget the dream of a boy.
Of course, I'll always be with you.
I'll always be with you, but I'll always be with you.
I'll always be with you, but I can't forget the dream of a boy.
You and You and You and I have a nice dream.
You and You and You are our only friends.
I have nothing to say, no matter how much I feel, I won't let you go
You will regret it
I realized how much it has happened that time
and I don't understand what happened
since you are in the middle of nothing
I don't even know if I can return to the world.
But it's not the first time I've ever been in this world.
I feel like my family and friends are getting closer to me.
And I'm happy to be together with Muka Muka!
Muka Muka and I are together!
I'm going to become a good weather!
Muka Muka!
Hi, Mr. Ohio.
You must feel good.
It's so warm!
It's warm.
I'm not the kind of guy who makes me feel like I'm doing it.
Can you please get me some water?
Well, now.
I can't get water.
That's right.
Because I'm full of time for you.
Okay, I'll do it.
Well then, shall we go once more?
Yes, let's go together.
That's great.
I'm sure I'll be able to get to this world and become a great fool.
I'm sure I'll be able to get to this world.
Golly.
The
time machine is in the
Old world by the time machine
should go back. But the time machine
will not be started from the side of naarost
well, look at it for a bit.
It's enough, not enough, because it has only
the
Hey hey, hey!
Hey hey!!
Hey hey hey!!
Hey, hey, hey!
Hey!
It's okay.
You heard me saying this.
That's why it seems to be a dangerous word for the sun.
That's the situation,
even as the earth is falling,
isn't it?
I don't know what's going on, but...
I don't believe it.
I was in the first place in the first place.
I was only 15 years old.
That's what I'm doing right now.
Why did you become like that?
I think the environment has changed a lot.
But I think this is easier to deal with.
That's right. My father is a bit of a stranger in this world.
I see. If you're father, you might know how I feel about Uemun.
What?
Alright. If you're a normal person, please leave your father alone.
Uemun is a good person, too.
If you live here, you can take care of the environment.
But there's another problem.
What?
I see. Uemun was a big brother in the past.
It's hard to live from now on, right?
Uemun will be a bit worried.
I see.
It's not a big deal.
I think I can take care of the environment.
Alright. Let's go.
Let's go.
My father is a bit of a stranger in this world.
I'm going to be a kid.
Hey, yeah!
Hey, brother.
You're always worried about me, baby.
I'm not going to play with you.
I'm going to be a kid.
I want to be a kid.
Hey!
Hey, you know what I'm saying?
I'm not going to play with you.
Hey!
Brother!
I'm glad you're here.
I'm going to play with you.
Brother!
Hey!
It's delicious.
Have a good meal.
What's wrong?
You're not going to play with me, right?
What?
Brother!
I have a favor.
I'm not going to play with you.
What are you talking about?
I'm going to play with you.
I'm going to be a kid.
I don't think I can play with you.
Yo-chan! What do you mean?
Ah, no, that's not the meaning.
Yo! What's wrong with the top?
Ah, Dari-chan! That's still a bad old man.
Oh, that's a lot of trouble.
Hey, yo!
On the top of the mountain, the top of the mountain,
the top of the mountain, the top of the mountain, the top of the mountain,
is what I like.
It's a bit...
It was an idea.
In such a heavy paper,
no matter how big theleigh is,
it's up to you, don't you?
Hey!
The bread of the thick rice cake.
Wow.
This is the least we can use
as cake for this part.
Oh, it's amazing!
It's a cake cake.
The cat from Russia also
has a good story, so...
Tianti!
The cat from Japan is the most dense.
The cat from Russia too,
the cat from Russia is the easiest to use!
Huh?
Hey, it's a fake.
It's a fake?
What?
It's a fake!
Stop it!
Come on, come on!
It's a fake!
What the hell are you doing?
It's a fake?!
It's a fake!
Eeeegg
Wow, it's really close!!
It's close!!
ITAHA
Long time no see!!
EEEAA, EEEEEEER, HE hp
Ge obe
GO
GREEET
WAIT
Bye?
Uyaaah! Uyaaah!
Nigarigo?
Eh? Did you say you were going to stop me again?
That's right.
I don't care about anything, but I can't stand it anymore.
Let's go back to this place!
The lemon is back!
Uyaaah!
What's wrong with this time?
If you think you're out of your mind, you can go back home.
I don't know what to do.
Uyaaah!
Nigarigo!
I'm going to eat it.
Hey, hey, Uemon.
I'm not here.
Come out here.
Hey, Uemon.
Uemon, come out.
I think you can't do it, Dad.
What are you saying?
I was trying to make it look like this.
I'm going to make it look like this.
Hey, Uemon.
Uemon.
Come out.
Uemon, what happened?
It's getting better.
Uemon, come out.
Uemon, you are in a way.
Uemon.
It's not coming back.
Uemon, come out.
Uemon.
I'll give you a round of applause.
Don't get too close!
Wait! What are you doing?
Stop it!
What's going on?
I don't know what's going on.
This is a 3-speed mission.
3-speed? What is this?
Look, it's the same as the jump.
The power is low, but the power is low.
So, if you lose the power of the jump,
You don't have to explain to that person, so you have to do something.
Okay, okay, okay!
I love you!
No, it's not.
I'm sorry, it's too late, but I'm scared to go to the top.
Let's go home.
Please wait.
See you later.
Do you see the front door?
Yes, it's a waste.
Anyway, I have to go back to the top.
Well then, Uemon is this mom.
Uemon...
Uemon, Uemon, why did you become like that? Tell me.
Uemon, Uemon!
Eh?
Uemon! Uemon!
Let's go to battle, Uemon!
Uemon, Uemon!
Uemon, Uemon, Uemon, how's Uemon?
Uemon...
Hey, it's correct.
Uemon, Uemon!
Good morning, Uemon.
Uemon-chan!
Uemon, Uemon!
This is the first time I've ever met you, so I've been waiting for you all the time.
That's right, I thought so.
Oh, Father!
I liked the sound of the voice and sound of the voice of the elementary school students.
Did you see the people you were looking at in this world?
I see.
I see. Father and I were just talking and I didn't see the crowd on the screen.
I was looking at the people you were looking at in elementary school students.
And that's not the way you were looking at the people you were looking at in elementary school students.
Oh, yes. We were good.
So you were trying to make a mistake.
I didn't expect you to make a mistake.
Even if you were looking at the elementary school students, it's a school's state.
Alright, I'll try my best to make a mistake.
Now, let's make a mistake!
Let's make a mistake!
Oh, I see.
I'm going to be able to make a mistake in the classroom.
The way you were looking at the people you were looking at in elementary school students.
I'm going to be able to make a mistake.
Alright, let's make a mistake.
Have a try.
Father, are you ready?
Yes, I am.
I'm going to be the daughter of Suzupa.
I'll be the daughter of Suzupa.
I'm not a big fan of the kids.
I'm a big fan of the kids.
I'll take it to the sea.
Oh, there it is!
It's a nice sea to be able to ride for 3 hours.
I'm so excited!
I don't think a lot of people will come.
Yay!
What are you doing, baby?
Ah, Rock!
Rock!
You're all five and you're all coming to the sea!
Yes, I'm coming to the sea.
I'm waiting for you!
Now, let's do it!
Come on, let's go!
What are you doing here?
Oh, you're right. I've got a good place to go.
We're going to the entrance.
The entrance? What do you want?
You don't believe me?
Let's go.
Hey, hey, hey, you!
How about a cute pet?
Oh, I see!
Then, let's go!
Good luck!
This is the best game!
Oh, you're right. We're not in the same shop as the shop we're in.
How's it? Is it cute?
It's so cute to see an old man.
How about this?
It's so cool, so you can eat it all together.
Aaaaaaaah...
I'm so happy that I've got a new one.
Anyway, if you're happy,
this is great too.
Oh, you can't eat all the food in your shop.
I'll just eat it all together and eat it all together.
It's a fish!
I'm going to get it!
Muka Muka, you're getting a little bit more.
Muka Muka!
Mika Muka!
Huh?
Muka Muka is not cute, Muka Muka?
Muka Muka!
Muka!
Huh?
This?
Muka Muka!
What?
Muka Muka wasn't cute, but it scared her to end up laughing.
Muka Muka!
Muka Muka is no good! Muka Muka is scared to end up laughing.
Muka Muka is not a good combination.
Yeah!
Let's do it!
Let's do it, let's do it!
I feel like I'm in Siberia for a moment.
Our fetters are the best!
Let's do it, let's do it!
Yay!
I'm so happy!
Idol Ali!
See you again!
Is it because I feel like I'm sleeping?
I'm also sleepy at home,
I'm so happy that I'm able to take care of the rest of my work.
Oh, that's right.
I'm going to take care of the rest of my work.
That's good, isn't it?
I feel like I'm going to take care of the rest of my work.
Hi, Hi, Hi.
I heard that you were taught at Uemon, right?
That's right.
I was a reserve when I was in Hawaii, right?
Yeah, I was in Hawaii, and I'm a reserve reserve.
But I'm sure I'll be able to do it well for the first time in a while.
What?
I'm going to take care of it!
That's right, Umi.
I'm going to take care of the rest of my work.
I'm home.
I'm home!
Let's go home!
I'm going to take care of the rest of my work.
Oh, that's right!
Mugamuka, hurry up and get out of here!
Aaaaaaah!
Huh? You've started the search!
What do you mean?
Next time, Mugamuka Paradise!
Mugamuka and Hankyojin!
See you again!
Mugamuka!